<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tell en-Nasbeh on Daily Life in Biblical Times</title>
    <link>/categories/tell-en-nasbeh/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tell en-Nasbeh on Daily Life in Biblical Times</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/tell-en-nasbeh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Post #2</title>
      <link>/blog/blog-post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/blog-post-2/</guid>
      <description>The examination of Shimeah&amp;rsquo;s daily life will primarily focus upon the grape harvest and his interactions with his extended family. Secondary topics will include food processing and storage, the structure and function of the four-room house, and the lingering effects of Sennacherib&amp;rsquo;s invasion of Judah. For most of the day, Shimeah will glean grapes from harvested vineyards alongside his mother Naarah. He will also return to his four-room house to press the grapes into wine and dry them into raisins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Post #1: Introducing Shimeah</title>
      <link>/blog/blog-post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/blog-post-1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Meet Shimeah. He is a 10-year-old boy who lives in Mizpah with his mother, Naarah, during the year 693 B.C.. His father died 8 years ago, when Sennacherib of Assyria invaded Judah in 701 B.C., leaving Shimeah an orphan and Naarah a widow. As a fatherless child, he is partially protected by laws that require Judahites to leave gleanings in their field for the foreigner, the widow, and the orphan, but he is still part of a socially and economically disenfranchised group.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>